tyba.com 2012-11-07

# Tyba - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Tyba we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

Tyba Solutions Ltd. (“Tyba”) operates several websites including tyba.com. It is Tyba's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Tyba collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Tyba's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Tyba's visitors use its website. From time to time, Tyba may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Tyba also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments or messages on Tyba.com websites. Tyba only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that website commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the website where the comment was left.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Tyba's websites choose to interact with Tyba in ways that require Tyba to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Tyba gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at Tyba.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Tyba - by purchasing upgrades or premium features to their websites, for example - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Tyba collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Tyba. Tyba does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Tyba may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Tyba may monitor the most popular websites of the Tyba users. Tyba may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Tyba does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Tyba discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Tyba's behalf or to provide services available at Tyba's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Tyba's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Tyba will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Tyba discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Tyba believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Tyba, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Tyba website and have supplied your email address, Tyba may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Tyba and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Tyba takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Tyba uses cookies to help Tyba identify and track visitors, their usage of Tyba websites, and their website access preferences. Tyba visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Tyba's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Tyba's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If Tyba, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Tyba goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Tyba may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Tyba and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Tyba may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Tyba's sole discretion. Tyba encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Tyba.com account, you should also check your website's dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
